欢迎加入OCR小组 qq群906722936 字幕优先发布于群内
我们的患者今早怎么样
How is the patient this morning?
你的未来在苏格兰场
Your future's at Scotland Yard.
我觉得这没什么可怀疑的
I don't think that's ever been in question.
我说的不是工作
I'm not talking about work.
前情提要
P R EV IO U S LY
你好啊 伊莱沙
Bonjour, Eliza.
你根本没必要回来
There's really no need for you to be here.
我要留在伦敦 直到这边的业务走上正轨
I'm staying in London until this ship is back on course.
我要去纽约了
WILLIAM: I'm going to New York.
一年吗
For a year?
这不是告别
WILLIAM: This isn't goodbye.
只是暂时分开
It's goodbye for now.
早 小姐 信
Morning, misspost.
谢谢
Thank you.
-天  -是呢
Goodness. Indeed.
早上好 伊莱沙
Good morning, Eliza.
克拉伦斯
Clarence.
我希望里面别都是账单
I hope that's not full of bills.
申请
Applications,
我们招新警探的广告
We've had an overwhelming response
收到的回复也太多了吧
to our advert for new detectives.
看来我还真是声名在外啊
I suppose my reputation does precede me.
我倒觉得应该是他们听说了女侦探的事吧
It's more likely they heard of the female detective.
广告上说的很清楚这里管事的是谁
The advert was quite clear who they'd be dealing with.
那谁的名字挂在门上了呢
Remind me whose name is above the door.
你的 和你儿子们的
Yours, and your sons'
机不可失
Well, no time like the present.
我们开始吧
Shall we begin?
这个不错
Oh, this one's good.
在弓街23年 你觉得这说明了什么
23 years at Bow Street- - what does that tell you?
说明他没有野心
That he lacks ambition.
跟塞缪尔·沃尔什先生不一样
Unlike Mr. Samuel Walsh.
连警探这个词都拼错了
Can't spell the word"detective. "
还有犯罪
Or the word"criminal"
或者他自己的名字
Or his own name.
去年解雇的
Fired him last year.
-他呢  -太年轻了
Him? Too young.
他太老了
He's too old.
不信任他
Don't trust him
不喜欢他
Don't like him.
他还在牢里呢
He's been in prison.
至少这个人我们能达成一致吧
Surely we can at least agree on this chap.
这个人我已经拒绝过两次了
I've said no to him twice already.
-别再试图把他的简历偷偷塞回来了  -我们都看了一整天了
Stop trying to sneak him through. We've been at this all day,
到目前为止我选的你一个都看不上
and so far you've liked none of my choices.
你也不喜欢我选的啊
Any more than you've liked mine.
跟他们共事的是我
It'll be me who works with them.
给他们付工资的是我 我才是老板
And me who pays for them- I am the boss.
你都提醒过我好多遍了
So you keep reminding me.
肯定会有能让你们俩都满意的申请吧
Surely some of the applicants are acceptable to you both.
问他啊
Ask him.
早上好
Good morning.
早
Morning
Morning.
我正在练字
I was just practicing my handwriting.
我怎么觉得你是在写信
Looked to me like you were writing a letter.
行吧
Fine.
我是在写信
I was writing a letter.
给谁
To?
巴纳巴斯
Barnabus.
丽兹
Lizzie!
看你到底在搞什么
What are you up to?
你为什么给威灵顿督查写信啊
Why are you writing to Inspector Wellington?
因为你不写啊
Because you aren't.
-什么  -他给我写信了
What? He wrote to me.
他说给你写了三封信
He said he's sent you three letters
但你一封都没回
and you've not replied to any of them.
我不想吃早饭了 上班要迟到了
I don't want any breakfast- - I'll be late for work.
丽兹 从威灵顿督查走了之后
Lizzie, you've not spoken of Inspector Wellington
你就没跟他说过话
since he's been gone.
也许这样做能让你心里舒服些
Perhaps it might help to do so.
你很明显在生他的气 也很难过
You're clearly upset and angry with him.
我不难过也没生气
I'm not upset, nor am I angry.
我好得不得了
I'm absolutely fine.
如果我们在一起
WILLIAM: If we are to be together,
那我就不能留在苏格兰场了
then I cannot remain at Scotland Yard
因为你是一个私家侦探
with you a private detective,
我也不能再陪在你身边 却
nor can I be around you anymore without...
却没有和你在一起
Without being with you.
有事
Yes.
抱歉打扰了
Uh, sorry to disturb,
但是纳什先生希望你能立刻去见他
but Mr. Nash would like you to meet him right away.
见他干嘛
What for?
去见一个新客户
To meet a new client.
什么新客户
What new client?
帕特里克
Patrick.
伊莱沙
Eliza.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
这个是未来
This...is the future.
前台 请问您需要什么
Reception- - may I help you?
-前台吗  -是的先生
MAN: Reception? Yes, sir.
-找布雷斯维尔先生  -没问题
MAN: Mr. Bracewell. CLERK: Certainly, sir.
-你了解电话吗  -不太了解
Do you know much about the telephone? Not much.
我知道它是由亚历山大·格雷厄姆·贝尔在1875年发明的
I know it was invented in 1875 by Alexander Graham Bell.
当然 关于是谁首先提出
There were, of course, counterclaims
这项创新的 也有其它不同说法
as to who first came up with the innovation,
但贝尔是第一个申请专利的人
but Bell was the first to patent it.
九年过去了
Nine years on, it's really only the preserve
考虑到安装和运行的成本
of the rich and the privileged,
它实际上只是富人和特权阶层的专利
given how costly it is to install and run.
尽管今年已经在各种公共场所
Although this year has seen telephone stations
安装了电话站
installed in various public places.
商店 电报局
Shops, telegraph offices.
回答是或者不是就够了
A yes or no would have sufficed.
正如你所说 普通人也更容易接触到它了
As you say, it's being made more accessible to ordinary folk.
这是新的淘金热
It's the new gold rush.
这个地方就处于最前沿
This place is at the forefront.
所以我们为什么来这
So, why are we here?
不列颠尼亚的所有者
The owner of Britannia wants us
希望我们帮忙否认一些糟糕的宣传
to negate some rather bad publicity.
是 布雷斯维尔先生
CLERK: Yes, Mr. Bracewell.
布雷斯维尔先生可以见你们了
Mr. Bracewell will see you now.
令人惊叹呢
ELIZA: Extraordinary.
可不是
It certainly is.
不列颠尼亚有一个工程车间
NASH: Britannia have an engineering workshop
他们在那里设计改进产品的新方法
where they design new ways to improve their product.
两天前 因为煤气爆炸而被摧毁
Two days ago, it was destroyed by a gas explosion.
死了两个人 一个年轻的发明家阿尔弗莱德·贝克
Two men were killed: a young inventor named Alfred Baker
和一个公司的联合创始人 乔治·戴维森
and the co- founder of the company, George Davidson.
所以是出现了煤气泄漏
So there was a gas leak.
根据报纸
According to the newspapers,
警方认为戴维森点燃烟斗
the police think Davidson lighting his pipe
是导致爆炸的原因
is what ignited the explosion.
但是煤气泄漏
But as for the gas leak,
看起来好像是有人故意破坏的
it seems someone tampered with the supply.
警方认为这个人
And the police believe that this someone
就是不列颠尼亚内部的人
works here at Britannia.
不是随便什么人
Not just someone.
而是我们的新客户 约瑟夫·布雷斯维尔
Our new client, Joseph Bracewell.
我的目标 纳什先生 就是让不列颠尼亚的电话
BRACEWELL: My aim, Mr. Nash, is to put a Britannia telephone
走进国内千家万户
into every household in the country.
等我们做到这一点
Once we've done that,
我们就会把目标转到国际市场
we will move into the international markets.
真为您的远大目标叫好 布雷斯维尔先生
I applaud your ambition, Mr. Bracewell.
我得承认 我还没用过电话呢
I must confess, I've not yet used one of these.
为了能尽全力帮到您 布雷斯维尔先生
To, to help you fully, Mr. Bracewell,
也许我们应该自己试试
perhaps we should try it ourselves.
请便
Be my guest.
下午好 不列颠尼亚交换所
OPERATOR: Good afternoon, Britannia Exchange.
请问您要拨打什么号码
What number do you require?
问证券交易所的号码
Ask for the stock exchange.
证券交易所 谢谢
Uh, the stock exchange, please.
正在帮您连接 请稍后
OPERATOR: Connecting you now- - please wait one moment.
问一下不列颠尼亚的最新股价
Ask for the latest Britannia share price.
证券交易所 请问有什么可以帮到您
CLERK: Stock exchange, how can I help you?
能拜托告诉我一下不列颠尼亚电话公司的
Uh, please could you advise on the current share price
最新股价吗
for the Britannia Telephone Company?
16-16
CLERK: One and six. One and six.
谢谢
ELIZA: Thank you.
再见
Goodbye.
这些可怕的宣传导致
All this dire publicity has caused the value
我公司的股价每小时都在下跌
of my company to fall by the hour.
这就是为什么我需要警察走开 而让你们介入
Which is why I need you to get the police off my back
找出该对这可怕行为负责的人
and find out who is responsible for this terrible deed.
他们甚至有个荒唐的说法
They have a ridiculous notion
说我想让乔治·戴维森死
that I wanted George Davidson dead.
你的合伙人吗
Your business partner?
我们一起创立了公司
We founded the company together.
我觉得是时候扩张了
I felt the time was right to expand.
买下我们的竞争者
To buy out our rivals.
而戴维森先生反对是吗
And Mr. Davidson disagreed?
这种分歧只是小问题
This disagreement was a minor issue,
我没理由因为这事要杀人
not reason for me to kill him.
我想警方之所以怀疑你
I gather the police suspect you
是因为本来你要和戴维森先生开会的
because you were supposed to attend this meeting
但你却没有按时出现
with Mr. Davidson, but you didn't turn up.
那天早上我们又吵了几句
We had another argument that morning.
我当时觉得不太想见他
I simply wasn't in the mood to face him.
就在办公室里待了一下午
I spent the afternoon here in my office.
但这很不寻常
But that was unusual,
不是吗
was it not?
你不参加每周一次的例会
That you didn't attend that weekly meeting?
据报纸所说 这是闻所未闻的
Unheard of, according to the newspapers.
不要相信报纸上说的一切
Do not believe everything you read in the newspapers.
你对另一个被杀的人有什么不满吗
Did you have any grievance with the other man that was killed,
那个年轻的发明家阿尔弗莱德·贝克
the, uh, the young inventor, Alfred Baker?
没有
BRACEWELL: No.
顺便说一句
And for your information,
阿尔弗莱德本来不应该出现在会上的
Alfred wasn't meant to be at that meeting.
这些问题都是必须要问的 布雷斯维尔先生
We have to ask these questions, Mr. Bracewell,
这样我们才能理清有关案子的细节
so that we're clear on all the details of this case.
既然如此 我就跟你说清楚
Well, in that case, let me be crystal- clear with you.
我没杀乔治·戴维森
I did not murder George Davidson.
至于阿尔弗莱德·贝克
As for Alfred Baker,
他设计的电话
he'd just designed the telephone
会让公司赚到大钱
that would make this company a fortune.
我怎么会想让他死呢
Why on Earth would I want him dead?
你到底为什么要那么质问他啊
NASH: Why in God's name did you interrogate him like that?
因为显然你不会问他什么有用的问题
You clearly weren't going to ask him anything useful.
我从没见过你如此敬畏一个人
I've never seen you so in awe.
我不是敬畏 我只是觉得他是个了不起的人
I was not in awe, I just think him an impressive man.
-有远见卓识  -我倒是觉得他挺讨厌的
A visionary. I think him rather unsavory.
你不同意我对人品的判断
Ah, you disagree with my judge of character.
真是意外呢
Quelle surprise.
那我的看法呢
What of my judgment?
现在负责办事处的是我
I'm the one who's going to be running the office
-我应该自己选择雇员  -我明白了
I should choose my own staff. Oh, I see.
原来是因为这事啊
That's what this is about, is it?
这就是你最近闷闷不乐的原因
That's the reason for this latest sulk du jour.
-我没有闷闷不乐  -我们可以晚点再讨论这个问题
I do not sulk. We will discuss this matter another time.
现在我们需要去看一下犯罪现场
Right now, we need to visit the crime scene.
终于有点能达成一致的事了
Finally, something we agree on.
去把我的马车叫过来
Go fetch my carriage.
菲尔普斯警探 巧了
Detective Phelps- - just the man.
很快就是菲尔普斯督查了
Inspector Phelps, actually- well, soon to be.
你要接手威灵顿督查的工作了吗
You're taking over from Inspector Wellington?
但现在还没有正式宣布
But there's been no formal announcement.
只需要盖个章的事
Just needs to be rubber- stamped.
那为什么还没盖章呢
And why hasn't it been?
肯定就是个时间问题
Well, I'm sure it's just a matter of time.
那我就先恭喜你的荣升了
May I offer my congratulations
这是你应得的
on what will be a well- deserved promotion.
那么你来这应该不是为了陪我聊天的吧
So, I assume your presence here is not just to keep me company.
说的没错
As ever, you assume right.
我们受雇调查不列颠尼亚的爆炸案
We've been hired to investigate the Britannia explosion,
我们想看一眼犯罪现场
and we'd like to take a look at the crime scene.
我想你们的消防专家已经评估过现场了吧
I take it your fire experts have assessed the scene?
还在等
Still waiting.
他们在其他地方被耽搁了 真是麻烦
They've been held up elsewhere, which is a bugger,
因为在他们查验现场之前
'cause we can't progress with the case
我们的案子也没法推进
until they've had a gander.
既然这样 那不如让我们
Well, perhaps in the meantime,
自己去看看
you might allow us to look for ourselves. Hm.
想得美 你们可以走了
Good one now hop it!
虽然你可能获得晋升 但你在礼貌方面
I see the prospect of a promotion hasn't endowed you
似乎没有什么提升 菲尔普斯警探
with any more decorum, Detective Phelps.
让我给你点建议吧 斯嘉丽小姐
Let me give you some advice, Miss Scarlet.
我现在是队长了
I'm the skipper now.
所以你要尊敬我一点才行
So you need to start showing me a bit of respect.
我一直觉得尊敬都是自己赢得的
Oh, I've always seen respect as something you earn.
斯嘉丽小姐就是这么喜欢开玩笑
: Oh, how Miss Scarlet does like to jest.
你肯定知道我们对你的尊敬是无需怀疑的
You surely know that our respect for you is unimpeachable,
菲尔普斯督查
Inspector Phelps,
而且我们也将不胜感激
and we'd be most grateful
绝对不能让他们进去
Under no circumstances let them inside.
是 长官
OFFICER: Yes, sir.
就算是女王亲自来
Even if the queen herself comes down here
说如果你不这样做就会因为叛国罪而被绞死
and says you'll be hanged for treason if you don't...
也不能让他们进
still don't let them in.
真顺利啊
That went well.
帕特里克 并不是所有人
Well, we're not all blessed
都有跟你一样口是心非的能力
with your powers of duplicity, Patrick.
如果你说的是用来维持我生意的
If by that you mean charm and persuasion
魅力和说服力
to keep my business afloat,
那么也许改天你也该试试
well, then perhaps you should try it sometime.
不管你喜欢不喜欢
Whether you like it or not,
你都得学会遵守游戏规则
you have to learn to play the game.
你到底是怎么了
What is wrong with you at the moment?
肯定不是雇佣员工的事
This can't just be about the hiring of staff.
是因为你的督查离开了吗
Is this about your inspector leaving?
我什么事都没有 他也不是我的督查
Nothing is wrong with me- - he's not my inspector.
我即将要说的话你可能不
What I'm about to say you may not like- -
实际上 你肯定不会愿意听
in fact, you definitely won't like it.
那你不如不说啊
Well, then perhaps you shouldn't say it.
到目前为止你在苏格兰场业务顺利
The work you've had up until now from Scotland Yard
都是因为你与威灵顿督查的友谊
has been on account of your friendship
我之所以能业务顺畅是因为我擅长自己的工作
with Inspector Wellington. I secured that work because I'm good at what I do.
我不质疑你的工作能力
And I'm not disputing that,
但尽管如此 你的友谊也还是帮了很大的忙
but the fact remains, your friendship helped a great deal.
但是现在菲尔普斯负责了
But now Phelps is in charge,
他可没有义务容忍你
he's not obliged to tolerate you.
容忍我
Tolerate me?
你到底想不想让办事处的业务
Do you want this business to flourish
在你的负责之下蒸蒸日上
under your command or not?
我当然想
: Yes, of course I do.
那你就得好好跟菲尔普斯相处
Then make it your business to get along with Phelps.
还有 你能别再郁郁寡欢了吗
And will you please stop sulking? !
我最后再说一遍 我没有郁郁寡欢
For the last time, I do not sulk!
那就好 因为我母亲就是个阴郁的人
Good, because my mother was a sulker
给我带来了很多不好的回忆
and it brings back bad memories.
行吧
Fine.
-你想让我做什么 回到他身边卑躬屈膝吗  -不用
What do you want me to do, go back to him and grovel? No.
你已经错过机会了
That ship has sailed.
我会尽量从正常的途径来
I'll attempt to obtain crime scene photos
获取犯罪现场的照片
from my usual source.
与此同时
Well, in the meantime,
我们也深挖一下两名受害者吧
let's do some digging on our dead men.
我建议我们从那个年轻的发明者开始
I suggest we start with the young inventor.
去跟他的遗孀聊聊
Speak to his widow.
看有没有人跟他有仇
See if anyone had a grudge.
你们俩看上去好幸福
You both look very happy.
你们结婚多久了 贝克太太
How long were you married, Mrs. Baker?
6个月
Six months.
叫我贝蒂就好
And it's Betty.
你丈夫是个狂热的读者
Your husband was an avid reader.
所有能搜罗到的工程的书他都有
He had every book on engineering imaginable.
是他的骄傲也是快乐
They were his pride and joy.
贝克太太
Mrs. Baker.
贝蒂
Betty.
你能想到谁对你丈夫怀恨在心吗
Can you think of anyone who had a grudge against your husband?
不着急慢慢想
And take your time.
丹尼尔·阿彻
Uh, Daniel Archer.
他也在不列颠尼亚工作
He, uh, works at Britannia.
阿尔弗雷德最初是他的学徒
Alfred started as his apprentice.
他当时就充满了怨恨
He was full of resentment
因为不列颠尼亚想采用阿尔弗雷德设计的新电话
'cause Britannia wanted to go with Alfred's design
而不是他的
for their new telephone, not his.
他的老板 戴维森先生 说他会一鸣惊人的
His boss, Mr. Davidson, said he'd be famous.
他说那是一项有独创性的发明
He called it"an ingenious invention. "
阿彻先生就很不开心
And Mr. Archer wasn't happy.
我丈夫认为他
My husband believed he tried
试图偷走他的新电话设计图
to steal his plans for the new telephone.
他为什么会这么想
And what made him think that?
他给藏起来了
He hid them.
在他办公室的地板下
Under the floorboard in his office.
作为保险 他说
As insurance, he said,
因为这个行业竞争太激烈了
on account of it being such a competitive industry.
然后上个月有一天
Then, one day, last month,
他发现阿彻先生在他的办公室里
he found Mr. Archer in his office
看上去鬼鬼祟祟的 我丈夫说
looking shifty, my husband said.
等他走了 阿尔弗莱德说
When he'd gone, Alfred said the rug
铺在地板上的地毯被掀起来了
that covered the floorboard had been disturbed.
阿彻先生怎么知道
How would Mr. Archer have known
你丈夫在哪藏了设计图呢
where your husband hid his plans?
阿尔弗莱德也想不通
Well, Alfred couldn't work it out.
戴维森先生不可能会告诉任何人
Mr. Davidson would never have told anyone.
他跟阿尔弗莱德一样担心
He was as worried as Alfred
想保守新设计的秘密
about keeping the new design a secret.
那现在设计图在哪
And where are the plans now?
阿尔弗莱德换了地方
Alfred moved them.
没告诉我放哪了
He didn't tell me where.
但他很确定阿彻先生一直在找
But he was certain Mr. Archer was after them.
所以阿彻先生 你一直在为不列颠尼亚
NASH: So, you're working on your own design
潜心研究自己设计的新电话
for Britannia's new telephone, Mr. Archer.
这将是一个很大的改进
Hm, it will be a great improvement,
尤其是在音质
most notably in terms
和可靠性方面
of sound quality and reliability.
我听说阿尔弗莱德·贝克先生
I understand that Alfred Baker
也设计了一个新电话
had designed a new telephone, as well.
他们称之为立式电话
They're calling it the Upright.
不幸的名字
: Woeful name.
不管它被叫做什么吧
Well, whatever it was to be called,
这个设计深受
the design was applauded
你们不列颠尼亚高层的赏识
by the powers- that- be here at Britannia.
阿尔弗莱德·贝克曾经是你的学徒 是吗
Alfred Baker was once your apprentice, was he not?
我教得好
And I taught him well.
但是被你的后辈赶超
But to have your junior surpass you...
一定很难吧
Must have been difficult.
竞争是好事啊
Competition can be a good thing.
达芬奇和米开朗基罗
Mm, da Vinci and Michelangelo.
安格尔和德拉克洛瓦
Uh, Ingres and Delacroix.
布雷斯维尔先生说他的设计
Well, Mr. Bracewell said his designs
会改变世界
were going to change the world.
但既然他和他的电话都没了
But now he and his telephone are gone,
你的路上就没有障碍了 阿彻先生
so the road is clear for you, Mr. Archer.
我还有工作要做
I have work to do.
你能告诉我们爆炸当天你在哪里吗
Can you tell us where you were on the day of the explosion?
在这 研究我的设计
Here, working on my design.
还有别人看见你吗
NASH: Hm, did anyone else see you?
你们不是警察
You are not the police,
我也没有义务回答你们的问题
and I'm not obliged to talk to you.
还有 能拜托你不要再碰我的东西了吗
And would you please stop touching my things? !
现在我们知道他是个暴脾气
NASH: Well, we now know he has a temper.
私家侦探的首要原则
First rule of being a private investigator- -
故意刁难嫌疑犯以试探他们的性情
deliberately vex the suspect to test their temperament.
帕特里克
Patrick,
我觉得我可以接受
I think I can just about take you
你对我商业技能的建议
advising me on my business skills,
但不要想当然地对我说教
but do not presume to lecture me on deduction.
我这里有一篇
There's an article in here
关于不列颠尼亚当前电话的文章
about Britannia's current telephone.
很明显 有三个主要问题
Apparently, there are three main issues:
成本 声音质量还有爱短路的倾向
cost, sound quality, and a tendency to short- circuit.
难怪布雷斯维尔如此迫切的想要一款新电话
No wonder Bracewell was so desperate for a new model.
克拉伦斯调查了一下
Clarence did some digging
布雷斯维尔的合作伙伴 乔治·戴维森
on Bracewell's partner, George Davidson.
然后呢
And?
他没有家人 没有近亲
He has no family, no close relations,
也没有财务问题或者跟谁有仇
no financial issues or known grudges.
除了他的合作伙伴
Well, apart from the one
约瑟夫·布雷斯维尔
held by his business partner, Joseph Bracewell.
别去调查咱们的客户了
Forget the client.
我们需要把精力集中到丹尼尔·阿彻身上
We need to concentrate on Daniel Archer.
他有很明显的动机 他想除掉自己的竞争对手
He has a clear motive, he wanted to remove his rival.
而且他没有不在场证明 他应该是我们的头号嫌犯
And he has no alibi- he should be our prime suspect.
你大都会警察局的朋友送来的
Delivery from your friend at the Met.
谢谢
Thank you.
不错
Hm, these are good.
非常不错
They're very good.
-犯罪现场吗  -嗯
The crime scene? Yeah.
太奇怪了
How peculiar.
什么
What?
这看起来像是气体被点燃时
That looks like the scorch mark from where
留下的焦痕
the gas was ignited.
所以呢
So?
如果像警方怀疑的那样 是戴维森的烟斗
Well, if, as the police suspect, it was Davidson's pipe
点燃了煤气
that ignited the gas,
为什么焦黄斑会出现在
why is the scorch mark on the opposite side
房间里尸体对面的位置上
of the room from the bodies?
动作快点 你们这些没用的懒虫
Hurry up, you useless vermin!
哪有时间慢吞吞的
We haven't got all day!
早上好啊 菲尔普斯警探
ELIZA: Good morning, Detective Phelps.
本来挺好 可惜你出现了
Yeah, it was, before you turned up.
我们想问问你们的消防专家
We wondered if the Britannia explosion
是否已经分析过不列颠尼亚的爆炸了
had been assessed yet by your fire expert.
他们现在被该死的圣奥尔本斯的一场工厂大火困住了
They're now stuck with a factory blaze in bloody St. Albans.
赶紧动起来
Get a move on!
我能说一句吗 菲尔普斯警探
NASH: Dare I say it, Detective Phelps,
你的人力好像有点不足啊
you seem a little overstretched.
可以这么说吧
That's one word for it.
让我们减轻你的负担吧
Let us lighten your load.
我们可以帮忙不列颠尼亚的那个案子
We can help with the Britannia case.
我不需要你们的帮助
I don't need your help.
功劳都归你
And let you take all the credit.
10分钟犯罪现场
Ten minutes at the crime scene.
只有这么多
That's all you're getting
我厉害的吧
Good, aren't I?
一定是这片区域有什么引起了火花
Something in this area must have caused the spark.
有人把这些电线的绝缘层割掉了
Someone has cut the insulation off these wires.
为什么要这么做呢
Why would they do that?
为了再连接时发生短路
Prone to short- circuit when connected.
这是不列颠尼亚电话的其中一个问题
It's one of the known faults of the Britannia telephone.
这才是引起煤气爆炸的原因 帕特里克
That's what ignited the gas, Patrick.
不是戴维森的烟斗
It wasn't Davidson's pipe.
是一个电话
It was a phone call.
也就是说 打电话的这个人才是凶手
Which means whoever made that call is our murderer.
伦敦有2512台电话在使用中
2, 512 telephones in operation in London.
你怎么知道这些事的
How do you know these things?
我做的研究啊 帕特里克 你应该也试试
I do research, Patrick- - you should try it sometime.
问题是 那个致命电话
The question is: from which telephone
是从哪部电话打出来的呢
was the fatal call made?
我想电话交换所会记录所有通话细节
I understand the telephone exchange log all call details,
因此可以向客户收取相应费用
so customers can be charged accordingly.
所以也许他们能帮我们缩小范围
So they might be able to help us narrow it down.
值得一试
It's worth a try. Mm.
只要我们能说服他们给我们看通话记录
Provided we can persuade them to show us their call log.
我怀疑所有的电话
I suspect all calls
都是具有私密性的 我们又没有搜查令
are treated confidentially, and we don't have a warrant.
苏格兰场的贝茨督查任您差遣
: Inspector Bates, Scotland Yard, at your service, madam.
就没有其他的警官吗
: Are there any other officers available?
贝茨督查有良好的业绩记录
: Inspector Bates has an excellent track record.
他最擅长个人工作
Well, he definitely works best alone.
所以当他去拜访交换所时
So, while he visits the exchange,
我可以继续进行有关电话的研究
I'lI continue my research into the telephone. Mm.
但我是否能进一步收集到有关
See if I can glean any further insight
阿尔弗莱德·贝克电话设计的信息
into Alfred Baker's new design.
怎么了
What?
你不郁郁寡欢时的样子更讨人喜欢
I much prefer it when you're not sulking.
我没有郁郁寡欢 我只是在沉思
I don't sulk- - I brood.
我知道在雇佣员工一事上我们意见不一致
I know we've been at odds over the hiring of staff,
但你最近真的不太对头
but you've not been yourself lately.
是因为督查吗
Is it the inspector?
他离开的事
The fact that he's gone?
贝茨督查在等着呢
Inspector Bates is waiting.
是 夫人
Yes, madam.
-我能帮到你吗  -当然
Can I help you? Of course.
下午好 你需要拨通哪个号码
Good afternoon, which number do you require?
当然 先生 请稍等
Certainly, sir- please hold.
安德伍德先生
: Mr. Underwood?
是我
Yes?
苏格兰场的贝茨督查
Inspector Bates, Scotland Yard.
你好 督查
How do you do, Inspector?
你们这的业务阵仗很大嘛
This is quite the operation you got here.
以前从没见过
Never seen one of those before.
他们允许我监听
Uh, they allow me to listen in.
确保我们的操作员状态良好
Ensure that my operators are performing at their best. Hm.
有什么事吗 督查
How may I help you, Inspector?
我在调查不列颠尼亚的凶杀案
I'm investigating the Britannia murders.
你在新闻上读到过吧
You read about them?
读过 太可怕了
I have- - terrible business.
我们需要确定某通电话的来源
We need to identify the source of a particular telephone call,
所以我想查看一下
so I'd be grateful to look at your call log
你9月21日当天的通话记录
for the day in question, the 21st of September.
好的 督查 稍等 我这就去拿记录本
Yes, Inspector, one moment, I'll just fetch the logbook.
稍等
OPERATOR: One moment.
抱歉督查
Sorry, Inspector.
我刚想到 我
It just occurred to me, I, uh
我应该先看看你的搜查令
Well, I should really see your warrant first.
搜查令
My warrant?
毕竟您也理解 我们的电话都是保密的
As you can appreciate, all our calls are confidential.
如果违反了规定 我是会丢饭碗的
It's more than my job's worth, uh, to break protocol.
当然您要是有搜查令就另说了
Unless, of course, you have a warrant.
行吧 好 我不是苏格兰场的督查
: AII right, fine, I'm not an inspector from Scotland Yard.
但如果你让我看通话记录
But if you allow me to see the call log,
我会保证你获益匪浅
I'll make it worth your while.
如果你不是警察 那你是什么
If you're not a policeman, then what the hell are you?
我是个私家侦探
I am a private detective.
一个什么
A what?
再也别想回来了
UNDERWOOD: And don't even think about coming back again!
我没报警就算你幸运
You're lucky I'm not reporting you to the police!
阿尔弗莱德·贝克与不列颠尼亚的合同副本
A copy of Alfred Baker's contract with Britannia.
-给我吧  -好
Oh, shall I...Uh, yes
好了
Yep, got it, got it.
谢谢
Thank you.
-你读过了吗 克拉伦斯  -扫了一眼
Have you read this, Clarence? Yeah, briefly.
乔治·戴维森和约瑟夫·布雷斯维尔
George Davidson and Joseph Bracewell
每个人会从新电话中
were each going to receive 45%of the profits
获利45%
from this new telephone.
可贝克先生 发明了电话的天才
While Mr. Baker, the genius that invented it,
却只能拿到10%
just got ten percent.
我在不列颠尼亚的联系人
Uh, my contact at Britannia
坚持要我拿瓶64年的靓茨伯
insisted on a bottle of Lynch- Bages '64
来换这份合同
in exchange for that contract,
所以我应该可以记到公司账上吧
so, I, I will, of course, be charging that to the company?
记到纳什先生头上吧
Oh, just charge it to Mr. Nash.
如遇其中一方死亡
"Upon death,
其个人利润份额
"an individual's share of profits
将平均分配给幸存的各方
will be distributed equally among surviving parties. "
你知道这意味着什么吗
You know what this means?
毫无疑问 买酒的钱我只能自掏腰包了
No doubt I will end up paying for that bottle of wine myself.
不是 意味着约瑟夫·布雷斯维尔
No, it means that Joseph Bracewell is now
现在可以获得阿尔弗莱德·贝克电话的所有利润
entitled to all the profits from Alfred Baker's telephone.
哦我
Oh, I'm
我很抱歉打扰你们 斯嘉丽小姐
I'm sorry to disturb you, Miss Scarlet.
怎么了 贝蒂
What is it, Betty?
我刚从阿尔弗莱德的母亲那里回来
I came back from visiting Alfred's mother.
可怜的老人家情况很不好
Poor woman's in such a state.
我走进家门时 听到有人从后门走了出去
And as I walked in, I heard someone going out the back door.
我吓坏了
Terrified, I was.
但当我过去看是谁的时候 人已经走了
But when I went to check, whoever it was had already gone.
我联系了警察 但是
I did contact the police, but
他们现在还没来
They still haven't come.
警局人手现在非常紧张
They're a little overstretched at the moment,
但你来找我是对的
but you did the right thing coming to me.
你确定没丢任何东西吗
And are you sure that nothing's missing?
我目前看到是没有
Nothing that I can see.
他们都没碰我的珠宝盒
They didn't touch my jewelry case.
虽然我也没什么珠宝吧
Not that I've got much.
这些书你有动过吗
Have you rearranged these at all?
那是阿尔弗莱德最喜欢的一套书
That was Alfred's favorite set of books.
第二本呢
Where's volume two?
之前在的啊
It was definitely there before.
这位是贝茨督查吧
ELIZA: Inspector Bates, I presume?
我听说贝茨督查计划失败
I hear Inspector Bates was thwarted,
所以你现在转向了第二套方案
so you resorted to plan B. Mm.
我把自己的档案反复看了两遍
NASH: I went through all my files twice
想看看有没有认识的人在这工作
to see if I knew anyone else who worked here.
我听说了 你办公室弄得乱糟糟的就走了
So I hear- - you left the office in quite a mess.
克拉伦斯可不开心了
Clarence was not happy.
所以你找到人了
So you found someone.
夜班经理 埃尔默·古德哈特
Mm, the night shift manager, an Elmer Goodheart.
不是说他这人有什么好
Not that there's anything good about him.
几年前 因为诈骗我把他送进了监狱
A few years back, I put him away for fraud.
他8点上班
His shift starts at 8: 00.
克拉伦斯跟我说贝克小姐家有人闯入
And Clarence said Miss Baker had a break- in.
拿走了什么
What was taken?
只丢了本书
The only thing missing was a book.
《改变世界的发明》第二本
"Inventions That Changed the World, "volume two.
就如此而已吗
And that's it?
但我有个理论
But I have a theory.
好啊
Oh, good.
我挺喜欢你这么说的
I like when you say that.
让我觉得内心特别温暖
It makes me feel warm inside.
你说完了吗
Have you finished?
说完了
Yes.
我认为书里有阿尔弗莱德
I think the book contained the plans
新电话的设计图
for Alfred's new telephone design.
就是丹尼尔·阿彻在找的那个
The ones that Daniel Archer was after.
他终于来了
Well, there he is.
埃尔默·古德哈特
Elmer Goodheart.
他看到我一定很开心吧
Sure he's going to be delighted to see me.
那是我说过话的主管 安德伍德先生
That's the supervisor I spoke to, Mr. Underwood.
-安德伍德先生  -嗨 查尔斯 谢谢你
Mr. Underwood. Hi, Charles- thank you.
他不过是个经理 却有自己的马车
He's only a manager, and yet he can afford his own carriage?
真引人注目啊
Striking, isn't it?
可不是嘛
It certainly is.
9月21日
The 21st of September.
感谢你的协助 古德哈特先生
Appreciate your assistance, Mr. Goodheart.
字迹可真工整
Handwriting is incredibly neat. Mm.
爆炸发生在2点36分
The explosion happened at 36 minutes past two.
在这
Here.
有个电话打给不列颠尼亚生产车间
A call was made to the Britannia engineering workshop
是
from the.
不列颠尼亚电话公司打过来的
Britannia Telephone Company.
布雷斯维尔的办公室
Office of J. Bracewell.
该死
Damn it.
我们绝对没法跟布雷斯维尔先生谈这事
On no account can we speak to Mr. Bracewell about this.
我们当然要跟他谈 帕特里克
Of course, we speak to him, Patrick.
他是我们的头号嫌疑人
He's our prime suspect.
可他也是我们的客户啊 可不少钱呢
He's also a client, and a well- paying one at that.
不行
No.
我们还是得继续盯着丹尼尔·阿彻
We keep our sights on Daniel Archer.
约瑟夫·布雷斯维尔从两人的死亡中获利巨大
Joseph Bracewell benefits financially from the two deaths.
他也承认了在爆炸时
He's admitted to being in his office
他人就在自己办公室里
with his telephone at the time of the explosion.
而我和你也达成了一致 打电话的那个人
And both you and I agree that whoever made that phone call
就是凶手
was almost certainly the murderer.
如果我们指控布雷斯维尔是凶手
If we accuse Bracewell of murder,
他就会开了我们俩 我们就没钱赚了
he will fire us and we'll lose our fee.
但我们是在做自己的本份啊
But we'll be doing our jobs.
不 你的本份就是
No, your job is to do
为我的生意着想 我现在就命令你
what's best for my business, and I'm ordering you
一个字都不能跟布雷斯维尔说
to say nothing to Bracewell.
命令我
Ordering me? !
对 我们盯着阿彻就行
Yes! We stay on Archer!
真好笑
It's laughable.
他不断的纠正我 告诉我该如何去做
He constantly corrects me and tells me how to behave,
可他做的事根本不符合道德
and yet what he's doing is completely immoral.
我从没见过这么冷血又偏执的人
I've never met anyone so bloody- minded and pigheaded.
在你开口之前 我要说 我可没有这两种毛病
And before you say anything, no, I'm not either of those things,
所以你还是别开口了 谢谢
so, I'll thank you to keep your opinions to yourself.
我什么都没说
I didn't say anything.
你不开口我也知道
You didn't have to.
威灵顿督查又给我写信了
Inspector Wellington wrote to me again.
他想知道你是不是生他气了
He wants to know if you're upset with him.
他为什么要问你呢
Why is he asking you?
他也想问你来着 可你不回信啊
Well, he tried asking you, and got no response.
丽兹 不管你说什么 我都知道你生气了
Lizzie, no matter what you say, I know that you're angry.
当你还是个小姑娘时
When you were a little girl.
我不需要一个巧妙设计的
I do not need a story
童年故事来教育
from my childhood cleverly designed to teach me
成年后的我
a life lesson as an adult.
你都不知道我要讲什么故事
You have no idea what the story was going to be.
肯定是有关狗的故事 不是吗
It was going to be about the dog, wasn't it?
行吧
Fine.
既然你懂得这么多 那你就自己解决问题呗
You know so much, you can sort things out for yourself.
没什么需要解决的
Nothing to sort out.
威灵顿督查离开了 等他回来时
Inspector Wellington has left, and when he returns,
我们可以好好谈谈 但在这期间
we shall talk, and in the meantime,
我没打算回复他的信
I have no intention of replying to his letters.
因为你生他气了
Because you're angry with him.
行吧
Finel
我就是生气了
I am angry!
他就不该离开
He shouldn't have left!
他应该留下 然后我们就可以
He should have stayed and we could have...
可以干嘛
Could have what?
我不知道
I don't know.
这就是你的答案
And there's your answer.
什么答案
What is?
他离开你的理由
The reason why he left.
他是为了你才离开的 当然也为了自己
He went away for your sake, as well as his,
这样你们俩才能有时间想清楚
so you both could have had time to work out
自己到底想要什么
what it is you really want.
他是个好男人 丽兹
He's a good man, Lizzie.
他不该被你如此冷漠忽视
He doesn't deserve you ignoring him like this.
哦 所以都是我的错咯
Oh, so all the fault lies with me, does it?
谢谢你的忠诚
Thank you for your loyalty.
-丽兹  -我真是受够你们了
Lizzie I've fed up with you,
帕特里克·纳什 还有其他说我做错了的人
Patrick Nash, and everyone else pointing out my faults,
非要告诉我该怎么做
and telling me how to behave that I,
可我完全有能力
as though I'm completely incapable
自己作出决定
of making my own decisions!
当然 布雷斯维尔先生
CLERK: Of course, Mr. Bracewell.
布雷斯维尔先生现在可以见你了
Mr. Bracewell will see you now.
你经常指控自己的客户谋杀吗
Do you often accuse your client of murder?
我不是在指控你 布雷斯维尔先生
I'm not accusing you, Mr. Bracewell.
我只是看证据做事
I'm just looking at the evidence,
而证据很明显
and it is compelling.
如果戴维森先生和贝克先生死了
You stood to gain all profits from the new telephone
你就能坐享新电话的所有利润
on the death of Mr. Davidson and Mr. Baker.
既然如此 我要给你讲个坏消息了
Well, I'm the bearer of bad news.
如果你认为那通电话是从这里打出去的
Because if that call came from this telephone,
那就不可能是我
then it couldn't have been me who made it.
因为我当时在伊灵
Because I was in Ealing.
伊灵
Ealing?
我在联合电话公司
It was at the United Telephone Company.
我一直在参与秘密谈判想买断它们
I've been involved in secret negotiations to buy them out.
那你一开始为什么
Then why not tell myself and Mr. Nash that
不告诉我和纳什先生
in the first place?
因为这是个竞争非常激烈的行业
Because it's a highly competitive industry,
我不想损害自己的生意
and I didn't want to harm the deal.
毕竟还没有成交
It's not yet been sealed.
也许你可以给我解释一下
Perhaps you could also explain
一个已经不存在的电话设计
how I can profit from a telephone
我要如何从中获益
that no longer exists.
贝克先生留下了设计图纸的副本
Mr. Baker made a copy of his plans,
我敢说你肯定是知道的
which I'm sure you well know.
我并不知道
I did not know.
斯嘉丽小姐 接下来你要这么做
Here's how this is going to work, Miss Scarlet.
你立刻把阿尔弗莱德·贝克的
You will bring me Alfred Baker's plans
设计图纸拿来
immediately.
如果你做不到
If you do not,
我就只能取消和纳什先生的合作了
I will let Mr. Nash know I'm firing his agency.
你去哪了
Where have you been?
M
Ealing.
伊灵
你不在的时候
Well, while you've been gone,
我们收到了布雷斯维尔先生的电报
we received this telegram from Mr. Bracewell.
他礼貌的提出
He advises, albeit politely,
我们的合作结束了
that we're fired.
你竟敢无视我的指示
How dare you disregard my instructions.
你让我别无选择
You gave me no choice.
我就是在尽自己的本份
I was doing my job.
你的本份就是保住我们的生意 而不是失去客户
Your job is to build this business, not lose us clients.
你去伊灵到底是要干什么
What the hell is in Ealing, anyway?
我去查布雷斯维尔先生的不在场证明去了
Um, well, I was checking on Mr. Bracewell s new alibi.
然后呢
And?
他说的没错
It stands up.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
试图劝说布雷斯维尔重新考虑一下
To try and persuade Bracewell to reconsider.
如果你要负责这家办事处 你首先要学会的就是
If you are to run this agency, you must first and foremost
要如何做一个生意人
be a businesswoman.
除非你能劝说我相信这一点
And Ill not be returning to Paris
否则我是不会回巴黎的
until you convince me you understand this.
纳什先生
CLARENCE: Oh, Mr. Nash
Mr. Nash!
斯嘉丽小姐
Miss Scarlet.
现在没空 克拉伦斯
Not now, Clarence.
我刚收到银行那边联系人的口信
I have just had word from my source at the bank.
他通知我丹尼尔·阿彻在过去的6个月里
He informs me that Daniel Archer has been making
一直在有规律的从账户里提钱
regular cash withdrawals over the last six months.
我说过现在没空了 克拉伦斯
I said not now, Clarence.
是 但还有件事
Yes, but just one more thing.
阿彻先生不到1小时前
Mr. Archer took out a large sum of cash
从自己的银行账户里提了一大比钱
from his bank account not one hour ago.
很高兴跟你合作
Pleasure doing business with you.
这是搞什么
What on Earth...?
我在你的抽屉里找到的 阿彻先生
I found this in your drawer, Mr. Archer.
是阿尔弗莱德·贝克先生最喜欢的书
It's Alfred Baker's favorite book, I gather.
其中一本被人从他的书架上偷走了
And one which was stolen from his bookcase.
正如我所怀疑的
As I suspected,
阿尔弗莱德把自己
this is where Alfred hid the plans
新电话的设计图纸画在了这里
for his new telephone.
你想把阿尔弗莱德·贝克的设计
You want to make Alfred Baker's design
据为己有
and pass it off as your own.
没有我的指导 阿尔弗莱德永远都不可能
Alfred could never have designed that telephone
设计出这款电话 所以
without my tutelage, so...
为什么功劳都给了他一人
Why should it be that he gets all the credit?
我刚刚看到你给了安德伍德先生一样东西
I just witnessed you giving Mr. Underwood something.
我想应该是钱吧
Money, I suspect.
给我看他给你的信封里的东西
Show me the contents of that envelope he gave you,
也许我就不去报警了
and perhaps I won't report you to the police.
是皮特曼速记
This is Pitman shorthand.
我父亲让我学过
My father made me study it.
是电话记录
It's transcripts from phone calls.
但都是阿尔弗莱德·贝克
But all involving Alfred Baker
跟他的老板乔治·戴维森之间的通话记录
in conversation with his boss, George Davidson.
你就是这样知道了他的计划 对吗
This is how you knew where he hid his plans, isn't it?
而要冒充是他的电话发明者
And to pass yourself off as the inventor
你就需要他死
of his telephone, you needed him dead.
不是这样的
That's not true.
而且你根本没有证据证明是我干的
And you have absolutely no proof that it was me.
好消息是 我们终于安抚了布雷斯维尔先生
Well, the good news is, we've managed to calm Bracewell down.
为了做到这一点
To do so,
我不得不说你
I had to paint you as, well
我猜猜 违反了指令
Let me guess- - insubordinate.
这么一想 也许我还是不告诉你
On second thought, it's perhaps best I do not
我到底用了什么词来形容你了吧
share with you the exact words I used to describe you.
你说的对
You were right.
我当然说的对
Of course, I was.
什么事我说的对
About what?
丹尼尔·阿彻
Daniel Archer.
现在我们只需要证明他是个杀人犯就行了
Now we just have to prove that he's the murderer.
我不是让你离开了吗
I thought Itold you to leave.
现在你还带了自己老婆来
And now I see you've brought your wife.
我不是他老婆
I'm not his wife.
我们知道你收人钱
We know you're being paid
比如像阿彻这种
by people like Archer to transcribe the conversations
然后帮人转录私人电话
of private telephone calls.
9月21日那天有一通电话
A call was made to the Britannia workshop
打到了不列颠尼亚的生产车间
on the 21st of September.
导致了爆炸
It caused the explosion there.
是丹尼尔·阿彻打的吗
Did Daniel Archer make that call?
我不知道
Um, I don't know.
听着 我什么都不知道 我发誓
Look, I don't know anything, I swear it.
这是你的吗
Do these belong to you?
对 但只是那些女孩的
Yes, but they're just timesheets
排班表
for the girls.
让我感兴趣的不是里面的内容
It's not the contents that interest me,
安德伍德先生
Mr. Underwood, but rather the,
而是你工整的笔迹
the neatness of the handwriting.
我们想再看一眼
We'd like to take another look at the logbook
9月21日的日志
for the 21st of September.
其它日期的笔迹都有所不同
The other days are varied with different handwriting.
应该是不同的接线员吧
Various operators, I assume.
可是谋杀发生那天所有的笔迹都是一个人的
The day of the murder has been filled entirely by one person.
就是你 安德伍德先生
You, Mr. Underwood.
为什么
Why?
有人让我这么做的
I was told to.
爆炸那晚
When this blackmail letter
这封勒索信
was delivered to me
被送到我这里
on the night of that explosion,
威胁说要曝光我的行为
threatening to expose me.
里面指示你修改打到不列颠尼亚车间的
It's ordering you to amend the details of the call
电话记录信息
made to the Britannia workshop
说是从约瑟夫·布雷斯维尔的办公室打出来的
to say that it came from Joseph Bracewell's office.
为了这么做
In order to do that,
我只能把电话记录本的一整页
I had to replace the whole page in the logbook
都重新誊写了一遍
and fill in the entire day myself.
那通电话到底是从哪打来的呢
So where did the call really come from?
从法灵顿的一个公共电话
From a public telephone in Farringdon.
写勒索信的人一定就是凶手
Whoever wrote that blackmail note must be our murderer.
他们很明显知道他的副业
They clearly knew about his sideline.
也许是在这里工作的人
Maybe it's someone who works here.
我也是这么想的
My thoughts exactly.
我再回去比较一下
I'll go back in and compare the handwriting
勒索信和电话记录上的笔迹
of the blackmail letter against the call log.
你去吧 我去趟法灵顿
While you do that, I'lI go to Farringdon.
如果运气好的话
With any luck, whoever runs
也许管理公共电话的人会留下记录
the public phones there will keep records.
一位才华横溢 正直诚信的侦探
"A talented detective with the utmost integrity. "
什么
What?
我就是这么向布雷斯维尔描述你的
They were the words I used to describe you to Bracewell.
我们不会做电话记录
CLERK: We don't keep records of calls made.
这电话用的人多吗
How often is this telephone used?
不多
Not much.
这附近的人
People around here,
都不太懂得这东西
they don't really understand it.
三天前 9月21日 有个顾客来用过电话
You had a customer here three days ago, on the 21st.
下午吧
Early afternoon?
你还记得那个人吗
Mm- - do you remember the person?
当然
Absolutely.
找到你了
: Got you.
BL
ELIZA: B. L.
跟勒索信上的笔迹是一样的
It's the same handwriting as the blackmail letter.
BL
B. L.
伊丽莎白·兰丁
Elizabeth Landing
她6个月前是这里的接线员
She was an operator here until about six months ago.
离开去结婚了
Left to get married.
你是说那封勒索信
: Are you suggesting that she was the one
就是她写的吗
that wrote me the letter?
肯定是
Almost certainly.
她是什么人
Who is she?
她未婚夫也在不列颠尼亚工作
Her fiance worked at Britannia.
她为什么自己签名写的是B而不是E呢
Why has she signed her name B and not E?
因为她称呼自己为贝蒂
: Because she called herself Betty.
你想让戴维森和布雷斯维尔死
You wanted Davidson and Bracewell dead.
但阿尔弗莱德 是个意外
But Alfred, that was an accident,
对吗
wasn't it?
阿尔弗莱德本来不该出席那次会议的
: Alfred was never meant to be at that meeting.
但他老板一定是在最后一刻突然叫他过去的
But his boss must have called him in last minute.
我根本不知道
I had no idea.
你偷了阿尔弗莱德
You stole the keys
生产车间的钥匙
to Alfred's workshop,
你在电话上动了手脚 让它起火花
you primed the telephone to spark,
刺穿了煤气管 然后离开了
punctured the gas pipe, and left.
知道那天下午
Knowing that by the afternoon,
布雷斯维尔和戴维森
when Bracewell and Davidson came
来开会的时候 车间就会像个炸弹一样
for their meeting, the workshop would be a bomb,
随时会爆炸
ready to explode.
然后你打了那通电话
And then you made the call.
10%
: Ten percent!
他们只给了他那么一点
That's all they gave him.
10%换回他投入的那么多时间和精力
Ten percent for all the time and all the work he put in.
我只是想阿尔弗莱德能得到应得的
I just wanted Alfred to have what he deserved.
太不公平了
It was so unfair.
随便你们怎么处置我吧
Do what you want with me.
反正我的生活也已经结束了
My life's over now, anyway.
我害死了自己的丈夫
I killed my husband.
我自己深爱的丈夫
: My own beloved husband.
我说进去了 你个混蛋
PHELPS: I said get in there, you toe- rag!
给我进去
Get in there!
你个白痴
OFFICER: You bloody idiot!
我觉得我做不到
I don't think I can do this.
我们向菲尔普斯保证过了
We gave Phelps our word.
如果我们让菲尔普斯拿到功劳 他就肯定会升职
If we give Phelps the credit, it could seal his promotion.
我们真的要跟他打交道吗
Is that really what we want, to be dealing with him?
需要跟他打交道的是你
It'll be you dealing with him.
所以你得让他赢才行
So you need to give him the win.
菲尔普斯警探
ELIZA: Detective Phelps.
斯嘉丽小姐
Miss Scarlet.
你有东西要给我吗
Have you got something for me?
证据都在里面了
The evidence is all in here.
提醒我一下
And just remind me
是谁破了这个案子
who solved this case.
是你 菲尔普斯警探
You did, Detective Phelps.
有人帮我吗
And did I get any help?
哪怕一点点
At all?
没有 菲尔普斯警探
No, Detective Phelps.
这才对嘛
That's the right answer.
怎么回事啊
What's going on?
我联系了你喜欢的那些候选人
NASH: Oh, I contacted the applicants you favored.
他们来这面试了
They're here for the interview.
那你去哪啊
Well, where are you going?
他们反正是要为你工作的
They'll be working for you.
所以你自己选择属下就好了
You should be the one to choose your staff.
我你有信心
Let's just call it a show of faith.
谢谢你 帕特里克
Thank you, Patrick.
我装了电话
I had that installed.
应该用的上
I thought it might be helpful.
干嘛 等你回巴黎后好时不时来检查我吗
What, to keep checks on me when you return to Paris?
你为什么非要往坏处想我呢
Why must you always think the worst of me?
我只是个走在发明前沿的人
I am simply a man at the forefront of innovation.
无论如何
Well, it's no matter.
这项技术还不足以
The technology is still far off being able
让我们打越洋电话
to place a call overseas.
但是作为一个走在发明前沿的人
But as a man at the forefront of innovation,
你肯定是知道的
you, of course, knew that.
我当然知道
Of course, I did.
你干嘛
What are you doing?
帮忙
Helping.
那么
So...
-你还在生我的气吗  -你还在生我的气吗
Are you still angry with me?
我先问的
I asked first.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
我不该背着你那么做的
I shouldn't have gone behind your back like that.
我只是觉得
I just thought
这样做才对
I was doing the right thing.
我知道 我也理解你为什么这么做
I know, and I understand why you did it.
而且你说的对
And you're right.
这件事 威灵顿督查离开的这件事
This, Inspector Wellington leaving
让我有点 心烦意乱
has caused me some...upset.
而且你也想他
And you miss him.
我这么说不是因为我爱你
I'm only saying this because I love you,
而是我认为给他回信会让你感觉好些
but I think replying to him would make you feel better.
你说的对
And Ithink you're right.
你总是对的
Oh, you're always right.
我总是这么跟巴纳巴斯说 可他就是不听啊
I keep saying that to Barnabus, but will he listen?
艾薇 我不喜欢吃西蓝花
Ivy, I hate cauliflower.
我做什么你就吃什么 年轻的女士
You'll eat what I cook for you, young lady.
晚上好
Good evening.
我是斯嘉丽小姐
My name is Miss Scarlet.
我想你是
I believe you are...
我父亲的一个同事吧
An associate of my father's.
他说这里有吃的
He said there'd be food.
对 我今天下午做了点熏火腿
Yes, I cooked a smoked ham this afternoon.
我给你切一片吧
I']l cut you a slice.
亲爱的威廉
Dear William,
我很高兴听说你在纽约
I'm happy to hear things are going well
一切都好
for you in New York.
这周很有意思
It's been an interesting week here.
但整体来说 算是不错的一周
But, on balance, a good one.
下集简介
纳什先生因涉嫌谋杀而被通缉
FITZROY: Mr. Nash is wanted in connection with a murder.
我有对他的逮捕令
I have a warrant for his arrest.
他们被杀之前
PHELPS: He was looking for someone
他在找人
right before they were killed,
然后他就消失了
and then he disappeared.
别管了
NASH: Leave this alone.
你逃离了凶案现场 要我怎么别管
How can I when you fled a murder scene?
我没时间解释了
I don't have time to explain.
你到底做了什么 帕特里克
What have you done, Patrick?